[
  {
    "answer": "Hypertext Markup Language",
"question": "the language for describing the proper formatting of text and images so that your Internet browser may display them as they are intended to look"
},
{
"answer": "hypertext",
"question": "a word, phrase or chunk of text that contains a link to another file or webpage"
},
{
"answer": "tag",
"question": "an HTML keyword written inside of triangle brackets. They usually are paired with a closing version that consists of: opening triangle bracket, a forward slash, the same HTML keyword, and closing triangle bracket"
},
{
"answer": "head",
"question": "contains important info about an HTML page, but is not displayed on the HTML page. It is placed between the html tag and the body tag. Typically contains the document title, character set, styles, scripts, and other meta information"
},
{
"answer": "body",
"question": "contains all the contents displayed within an HTML page, such as text, hyperlinks, images, tables, lists, etc."
},
{
"answer": "title",
"question": "defines a name for the browser tab and provides a name for the page when it is added to favorites/bookmarks"
},
{
"answer": "h1",
"question": "defines the most important headings in an HTML page"
},
{
"answer": "p",
"question": "defines a paragraph in an HTML page. Browsers will automatically give it a top margin and bottom margin."
},
{
"answer": "br",
"question": "inserts a single line break in an HTML page. It is an empty tag which means that it has no closing tag"
},
{
"answer": "bold",
"question": "text that is thicker, darker, and heavier than normal"
},
{
"answer": "italic",
"question": "text that is slightly slanted in order to give it emphasis"
},
{
"answer": "img",
"question": "defines an image in an HTML page. It has two required attributes: src and alt"
},
{
"answer": "alt",
"question": "provides alternative information for an image if a user cannot view it (because of an error in loading the image, slow connection, or if the user uses a screen reader)"
},
{
"answer": "ol",
"question": "defines a numerically or alphabetically sorted list in an HTML page"
},
{
"answer": "ul",
"question": "defines a bulleted, un-numbered list in an HTML page"
},
{
"answer": "li",
"question": "defines a list item in an HTML page. It must be placed within ol or ul tags"
},
{
"answer": "Cascading style sheets",
"question": "the language for describing the presentation of Web pages, including colors, layout, and fonts"
},
{
"answer": "Inline CSS",
"question": "used to define a style for a single HTML tag. For example, h1 style="color:blue;""
},
{
"answer": "Internal CSS",
"question": "used to define a style for a single HTML page, this code is placed within style tags inside of the head section"
},
{
"answer": "External CSS",
"question": "used to define the style for one or more HTML pages. It allows you to change the look of an entire web site by changing one file."
},
{
"answer": "CSS rule",
"question": "a statement that tells browsers how to render a specific HTML tag. It consists of a selector, curly bracket, one or more declarations, and a closing curly bracket."
},
{
"answer": "CSS selector",
"question": "the name of the HTML tag that will be styled by the following declarations."
},
{
"answer": "CSS declaration",
"question": "a CSS property paired with a value. For example, color: blue;"
},
{
"answer": "Hexadecimal",
"question": "a base-16 number system that uses the values 0-9, A, B, C, D, E and F"
},
{
"answer": "CSS box model",
"question": "a set of CSS properties that wrap around every HTML element. It consists of: margins, borders, padding, and the content"
},
{
"answer": "Padding",
"question": "a CSS property that generates space around an elementâ€™s content within the border"
},
{
"answer": "Border",
"question": "a CSS property that creates a line around the padding and the content"
},
{
"answer": "Margin",
"question": "a CSS property that creates space around an element, outside of the border"
},
{
"answer": "Font Stack",
"question": "CSS code that tells a browser what typeface to display and what backups to use if the first choice is not available"
},
{
"answer": "Serif Font",
"question": "a typeface that contains small extra lines at the ends of characters. For example, Times New Roman"
},
{
"answer": "Sans Serif Font",
"question": "a typeface that does not use small lines at the ends of characters. For example, Arial and Helvetica"
},
{
"answer": "table",
"question": "an HTML element for creating rows and columns on a Web page"
},
{
"answer": "tr",
"question": "defines a row in an HTML table and contains one or more th or td elements"
},
{
"answer": "th - 	a header cell in an HTML table"
},
{
"answer": "td",
"question": "a normal data cell in an HTML table"
},
{
"answer": "255, 255, 255",
"question": "RGB values for white"
},
{
"answer": "255, 255, 0",
"question": "RGB values for yellow"
},
{
"answer": "0, 255, 255",
"question": "RGB values for cyan/aqua"
},
{
"answer": "255, 0, 255",
"question": "RGB values for magenta/fuchsia"
},
{
"answer": "0, 0, 0",
"question": "RGB values for black"
},
{
"answer": "#FFFFFF",
"question": "Hexcode for white"
},
{
"answer": "#FF0000",
"question": "Hexcode for red"
},
{
"answer": "#FFFF00",
"question": "Hexcode for yellow"
},
{
"answer": "#00FF00",
"question": "Hexcode for green"
},
{
"answer": "#00FFFF",
"question": "Hexcode for cyan/aqua"
},
{
"answer": "#0000FF",
"question": "Hexcode for blue"
},
{
"answer": "#FF00FF",
"question": "Hexcode for magenta/fuchsia"
},
{
"answer": "#000000",
"question": "Hexcode for black"
}
]
